

PRIYANKA WAGHMARE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+91-9370067523

priyankaw483@gmail.com

https://github.com/propriyanka

https://www.linkedin.com/in/priyankawaghmare-17246a239

EDUCATION

2016 B.E. IT (75.42%) SGBAU with Distinction 2012 H.S.C. (65.33%) Maharashtra State Board 2010 S.S.C. (88.00%) Maharashtra State Board

PROJECTS

(2023- present)

1. Captured Katha's (Personal Blog)

https://capturedkathas.com/

Static personal blog website under construction using front-end tech. An elegant platform for sharing insights and experiences. Clean, modern design, HTML, CSS-powered. Elevating online presence with exceptional simplicity and accessibility.

2. Tic-Tac-Toe (2023- present)

Developed interactive Tic-Tac-Toe game using React. Delivered engaging user experience with dynamic gameplay and responsive design. Optimized performance with efficient code.

ABOUT ME

Versatile, high-energy, career-oriented professional, offering 4+ Years of dynamic career in IT and Marketing. Collaborative team player with a successful track record of working closely with designers, back-end developers, and stakeholders to deliver high- quality web solutions. Committed to staying current with cutting- edge front-end technologies and industry trends.

EXPERIENCE

Computer Programmer

Maharashtra State Horticulture & Medicinal Plant Board Mar 2020 - May 2022

Employed a variety of languages to create user-friendly web pages, translated necessary requirements into HTML, and ensured the enhancement of the company's website. Developed and maintained daily, weekly, and monthly operational analysis.

Web Marketing Executive

Research Reports Inc.

Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

Responsible for Search Engine Ranking, Social Media Marketing, Competitive Analysis, Website Analysis, Email-Marketing, Lead Generation, and Content Writing.

LANGUAGE

Hindi

English Marathi

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5,CSS3

JavaScript

Bootstrap

React.js